Hello friends,
you are heartily welcome to the Stock India YouTube channel and
friends, in this video we are going to talk about
insurance,
they have been updated, so in this we
will talk about the results of Q3 and
before discussing the Q3 results, let us talk about the stocks today, so
in today's session, there is a rise of more than
one percent in the stocks
and the stocks are trending at 1254
and if we talk about the maximum returns of the company, then the
company has
generated a return of 84% so far and if we
talk about the last one year, then if we talk about the last one
year
percentage, then
this HDFC
Bank is a subsidiary company
and if we talk about its market cap, then a
market cap of 61000 crores can be seen
and the week 52 of the stocks which has
come is 1465 and the week 52 which is
going on is 1001 and if we
talk about the present, then the stocks which are there in the present are
trending at 1254 and
Talking about the details of the last six months,
even in the last six months, the companies are also
seen to be down by a shaded percentage,
although it is an Anubhav company and a
much better company is seen
in the general insurance sector and
big returns can be seen in this too, let's go to the
result PDF and further we have
reached the PDF of such people and first of all we will
talk about its audit statement and detailed
results and the consolidated results of the company are
visible and
so let's talk and this is the quarter of 31 December 22, this is of
September 22 and this is the
quarter of December 21, so this company is a general
insurance company, so
in the general insurance company, first of all, if
we
read the revenue from operations in the companies column, then in it
we will get the
first gross premium return
[music] which is of
786 crores, it was in December 21 and if we
talk about September 22, then it was 5300 ₹2 crores
and if we talk about the present quarter, then it is of
5599 crores  The gross premium of the company is being
seen and if we
talk about the net premium of the company, if we talk about premium and net
premium, then it was
3311 crores in the quarter of December 21 and
3836 crores in the quarter of September 22 and if we talk about the present quarter, then
it was
₹372 crores, so year to year
jumps are being seen in it, so when it is
seen that it increases from 311 to 3792
crores
and in this quarter, the
latest quarter in which 37002 crores are being
seen, then a
decline of around 100 crores is being
seen in it and now we talk about the
income of the company, in that respect, the
company also earns income from investment in the company and if there is foreign exchange in income, then if
we talk about the total income in it, then the total
income of the company was 1854 crores in the quarter of December 21
and in the quarter of September 22
4499 crores and if we talk about the present quarter, then the
year to year income is 4362 crores,
but if we compare quarter to
quarter, then after deducting from 4499, the
total income is 4362 crores
and now if we talk about the total expenses of the company, then
this is the
column of total expenses and if we talk about the total expenses, then if we talk about the
quarter of December 21, then
in the quarter of December 21 it was
3581 crores and if we talk about the quarter of September, then it was
3988 crores and if we talk about the present quarter, then it is
seen to be
485 crores, so in this column the
total expenses are
seen to be increasing a lot in this quarter, the year to year income of the company is
also big and quarter to quarter also we are
seen to be increasing and now let
us see the total profit for D column of the company,
our profit before tax column  And
after tax,
how much profit is the company getting after tax,
which we
call profit after tax,
this was the quarter of December 21, in the quarter of
December 21, in the
quarter of December 21, it was 317 crores,
in the quarter of December 22, it was 590 crores
and if we talk about the present quarter, then it was
₹352 crores, so if we look at it, then year 2
year it is big
but this quarter is
590 crores
[Music] If we
talk about the quarter of December 21, then the
running share of the company was 6.47 and
in the quarter of September 22, it is seen to be
12.03 and in the present quarter, the
app is seen to be 7.18, that is, in
year 2 year, it is
seen to be increasing, from 6.47 to 7.18, but
quarter to quarter it is seen to be down,
in the previous quarter, app was full, in this quarter
7.18 is seen, that is, the
company  The
quarterly results are getting affected,
so these are getting affected,
but the
year to year results are getting affected
and now let's talk about
banking and non-banking, let's
also see their NPS, how much is the company, in this, the
non-provisioning assets, which are
called, the gross and net NPS
of the company, in this the company has
shown black, this means that the company is
not seeing any kind of NPA at present
and this is a very good thing that the
company does not have any kind of NPA and the
gross and net NPS is also seen
to be zero in it, so if we talk about the company,
it is a very good company
and the results are also getting a
little down,
but if we talk about the year to year results of the company, then the year
to year
results are getting very good results for the
company and now let's
look at the company from point to point, which
points the company has given
and in which factors which results are there  The
growth in the factors that are being seen is such that if we
talk about the growth domestic premium income in this, the
premium of an insurance company is
called GDP, Gross Direct
Premium Income, so this income of the company
increased to
160 billion in 9 months of Finance Share 23, that is, if we
talk about 9 months, this
quarter, if we
talk about the last 9 months, then 160
billion has increased in 9 months and if we
talk about growth in this, then in the last 9 months the
GDP of the company has
increased by 20.6% in the last 9 months
and if we show this 20 point growth company, if we
talk about the insurance total insurance industry, then the growth of the insurance industry in the last 9 months,
in the last six months, in the last 9 months, is 20.6
percent, that is being seen, this
means it performed better than the industry, the
company performed better than the industry
and let us talk about the company, in
this the GDP growth of the
company was  19.9 and if we talk about this quarterly, then the
growth has been 19.9 and
this also the industry growth is 17.5 for 9 months,
finance layer 23 and what is there is
seen to be higher than this
and now let's talk about less
and quarterly,
how much growth has there been in the GDP of Q3,
its growth in Q3 was 16.0%, let's go
ahead and give against the industry growth
of 18 point one and in this, the growth of the industry
in quarter three, the
growth of the total insurance industry has been 18.1 and the
quarterly growth of the company is 16.0,
so the quarterly growth of the company is being
seen less
and if we talk about point, there is a jump of up to
34% in the profit after tax of the company
and this jump is of
how many months, nine months, we are talking about
that the result of 9 months is to be
seen much better for the company  It is being seen
and a jump of up to 34% is being seen in it
and let's talk about the
total net profit of the company, the
profit after tax is being seen up to 11%
and there is 3.53
billion in it and this is
3.18 billion in the quarter three financial year.
If we compare it with the previous quarter, then the
profit
after tax in this quarter is up to 11%, a
jump is being seen in it,
we are getting much better results in this,
although the quarterly
results are seen to be slightly out of place in it,
but the year to year results of the company are getting
better, so
friends, if
you liked this video, then visit the channel page for the first time, then
hit the bell icon and
select all as well, we will
meet again in the next video with the latest quarterly
results and till then, hello